Guide to the Lindseth Collection of Alice Ephemera MSS.368
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX: Media
  - Subseries B: Vinyl Sound Discs
    - Chick Corea "The Mad Hatter" Record, 1978 (Box 68)
    - Original Soundtrack Recording Joel Shaftel's Production of Alice's Adventures in Wonderland, 1972 (Box 68)
    - Original Soundtrack Recording Joel Shaftel's Production of Alice's Adventures in Wonderland, 1972 (Box 68)
    - Original Soundtrack Recording Joel Shaftel's Production of Alice's Adventures in Wonderland, 1972 (Box 68)
    - Alice in Wonderland and the Emperor's New Clothes, Rocking Horse Players and Orchestra, undated (Box 68)
    - The Simon Sisters Sing for Children Record, 1973 (Box 68)
    - Argo Presents Jane Asher as Alice in Through the Looking Glass 1 of 2, 1960 (Box 68)
    - Argo Presents Jane Asher as Alice in Through the Looking Glass 2 of 2, 1960 (Box 68)
    - Storyland, Twinkle Records, undated (Box 68)
    - Annie in Wonderland, Annie Haslam, 1977 (Box 68)
    - John Baldry, Everything Stops for Tea, 1972 (Box 68)
    - Walt Disney's Peter Pan and Alice in Wonderland, 1960 (Box 68)
    - Songs from Walt Disney's Alice In Wonderland, featuring the Lady in Blue June Winters, undated (Box 68)
    - Songs from Walt Disney's Alice In Wonderland, featuring the Lady in Blue June Winters, undated (Box 68)
    - Alice au Pays des Merveilles, Livre Disque Philips, 1962 (Box 69)
    - Alice au pays des Merveilles album disque audio visuel, undated (Box 69)
    - Alice in Wonderland, a Talking Book, complete and unabridged, 1954 (Box 69)
    - Alice in Wonderland Book and Record, Educational, Entertaining Peter Pan Records, undated (Box 69)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Meets the Caterpillar and Cheshire Cat and 'Twas Brillig, 1951 (Box 69)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Meets the Caterpillar and Cheshire Cat and 'Twas Brillig, 1951 (Box 69)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Meets the Caterpillar and Cheshire Cat and 'Twas Brillig, 1951 (Box 69)
    - A Musical Story: Alice in Wonderland, Peter Pan Players & Orchestra, undated (Box 69)
    - Alice in Wonderland, Peter Pan Players & Orchestra, undated (Box 69)
    - Alice in Wonderland, Peter Pan Players & Orchestra, undated (Box 69)
    - Alice in Wonderland, Peter Pan Players & Orchestra, undated (Box 69)
    - Alice in Wonderland, Musical Story, Peter Pan Records, 1961 (Box 69)
    - Listen Look picture book, Alice in Wonderland, 1941 (Box 69)
    - Listen Look picture book, Alice in Wonderland, 1941 (Box 69)
    - Walt Disney's Story of Alice in Wonderland with Songs from the film, 33-1/3rpm Long Play, 1965 (Box 69)
    - Walt Disney's Story of Alice in Wonderland with Songs from the film, 33-1/3rpm Long Play, 1965 (Box 69)
    - Walt Disney's Story of Alice in Wonderland with Songs from the film, 33-1/3rpm Long Play, 1965 (Box 69)
    - Alicia en el Pais de las Maravaillas, 45rpm, RCA Victor, undated (Box 69)
    - Disney Programs Alice in Wonderland Show'n Tell picturesound program, 1969 (Box 69)
    - Disney Programs Alice in Wonderland Show'n Tell picturesound program, 1969 (Box 69)
    - Disney Programs Alice in Wonderland Show'n Tell picturesound program, 1969 (Box 69)
    - Disney Programs Alice in Wonderland Show'n Tell picturesound program, 1969 (Box 69)
    - All in a Golden Afternoon from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951 (Box 69)
    - I'm Late and Alice in the White Rabbit's House, from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951 (Box 69)
    - A Very Merry Unbirthday, from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951 (Box 69)
    - Walt Disney's Alice In Wonderland (Title Song) and In a World of My Own, 1951 (Box 69)
    - Painting the Roses Red, and the March of the Cards, from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951 (Box 69)
    - Painting the Roses Red, and the March of the Cards, from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951 (Box 69)
    - Very Good Advice and Caucus Race from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951 (Box 69)
    - The Walrus and the Carpenter, from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951 (Box 69)
    - The Walrus and the Carpenter, from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, 1951 (Box 69)
    - White Rabbit by Jefferson Airplane, RCA 45rpm record, 1966 (Box 69)
    - Lewis Carroll: Alice in Wonderland, a children's music drama, 1947 (Box 70)
    - Rita Hassan and the American Repertory Theatre Present Eva Le Gallienne's Production of Alice in Wonderland and Through the Looking Glass, undated (Box 70)
    - Deems Taylor, Through the Looking Glass, Played by Howard Barlow, c. 1940 (Box 70)
    - Decca Records Ginger Rogers as Alice in Alice in Wonderland, 1944 (Box 70)
    - Riverside Presents Alice's Adventures in Wonderland read and sung by Cyril Ritchard with facsimile of first edition of the book, 1957 (Box 71)
    - Riverside Presents Alice's Adventures in Wonderland read and sung by Cyril Ritchard with facsimile of first edition of the book, 1957 (Box 71)
    - Riverside Presents Alice's Adventures in Wonderland read and sung by Cyril Ritchard with facsimile of first edition of the book, 1957 (Box 71)
    - Riverside Presents Alice's Adventures in Wonderland read and sung by Cyril Ritchard with facsimile of first edition of the book, 1957 (Box 71)
    - Alice in Wonderland Story adapted and produced by Douglas Cleverdon, Jane Asher as Alice, box set, 1958 (Box 72)
    - Alice in Wonderland Story adapted and produced by Douglas Cleverdon, Jane Asher as Alice, Stereophonic box set, undated (Box 72)
    - Through the Looking Glass and What Alice Found There, narrated by George Rose, with Sarah-Jane Gwillam as Alice., 1975 (Box 72)
    - Murray Hill Presents Through the Looking-Glass, Read and Sung by Cyril Ritchard with Facsimile of the book, 1958 (Box 72)
    - Murray Hill Presents Through the Looking-Glass, Read and Sung by Cyril Ritchard with Facsimile of the book, 1958 (Box 72)
    - Argo Presents Jane Asher as Alice in Through the Looking Glass, box set, 1959 (Box 72)
    - London presents Jane Asher as Alice in Through the Looking Glass, stereophonic box set, undated (Box 72)
- Oversize Series II: Housewares/Decorations
  - Grey on cream wallpaper, Tenniel illustrations, Undated; cuid6202; 2 items two sheets of wallpaper (Item MSS.368.cuid6202)
    Dimensions: 70"x23.5"
  - Grey on cream wallpaper, Tenniel illustrations, Undated; 2 items two sheets of wallpaper (Flat-file-folder 2)
    Dimensions: 52"x32"
  - Grey on cream wallpaper, Tenniel illustrations, Undated; 2 items two sheets of wallpaper (Flat-file-folder 2)
    Dimensions: 41"x40"
  - Tony Sarg Stenciled Wallpaper, [1930's]; cuid6201 (Item MSS.368.cuid6201)
    Dimensions: 59"x22"
  - Wall Hanging of the Caterpillar, [Undated] (Box 24, Item 1)
    Handmade wall hanging, hand-stitched on burlap, of the Caterpillar.
    Dimensions: 20"x24"
  - Alice in Wonderland Towel Set and Pillow Cases, [Undated] (Box 24, Item 2)
  - White Rabbit Felt Yellow Calendar, 1965 (Box 24, Item 3)
  - Alice in Wonderland Orange Felt Banner, [Undated] (Box 24, Item 4)
    Dimensions: 28.5"x14.75"
  - Paper Shopping Bag with Alice Characters, [Undated] (Box 44, Item 1)
  - Paper Shopping Bag with Alice Characters, [Undated] (Box 44, Item 2)
  - Paper Shopping Bag with Alice Characters, [Undated] (Box 44, Item 3)
  - Happy Un-Birthday Kit, 1962 (Box 44, Item 4)
  - Midsummer Night's Dream Calendar, Illustrated by Arthur Rackham, 1978 (Box 44, Item 5)
  - Alice's Adventures in Wonderland by Arthur Rackham, 1979 (Box 44, Item 6)
  - Alice in Wonderland and its Sequels; a Calendar of Pictures by 12 Artists for 1977 (Box 44, Item 7)
  - Alice in Wonderland and its Sequels; a Calendar of Pictures by 12 Artists for 1977 (Box 44, Item 8)
  - Alice's Adventures in Wonderland by Arthur Rackham, 1979 (Box 44, Item 9)
  - Classic Children's Book Illustrations to Decorate a Child's Room; Alice in Wonderland, [1950's] (Box 44, Item 10)
    Title: Classic Book Illustrations to Decorate a Child's Room; Alice in Wonderland
    Description: Set contains 22 Alice in Wonderland wall print cut-outs. Silkscreened.
  - Pink Felt White Rabbit Print on Board, [Undated] (Box 53, Folder 7)
    Dimensions: 15"x21"
- Oversize Series III: Games/Dolls/Toys/Puppets
  - Subseries B: Games/Puzzles
    - Tea-Time Plastic Dishes, 1945 (Box 26, Item 2)
      Title: Tea-time Plastic Dishes
      Description: "Hand painted Alice in Wonderland tea time dishes." 22 pieces, original printed box). Alice vignettes cast in relief, floral decorations painted by hand. NB: Alice is not mentioned or illustrated on the box — which suggests that the box is a passe-partout for many different styles of Plasco tea-sets.
    - Alice in Wonderland Game; Follow the White Rabbit Through Wonderland, 1974 (Box 34, Item data_value_missing_f668fcf01fe3f9faf44f8760404c7bce)
    - Looking Glass Chess set from Alice in Wonderland, 1966 (Box 30, Item 2)
    - Alice in Wonderland Paint Set, 1970 (Box 74)
      Title: Alice in Wonderland Paint Set
      Description: Alice in Wonderland paint set in a pictorial metal box. Paints and brushes unused.
      Dimensions: 9"x20"
    - Alice in Wonderland Picture Puzzle, [Undated] (Box 31, Item 2)
    - Alice in Wonderland Picture Puzzle, [Undated] (Box 31, Item 3)
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 1/8, 1971 (Box 31, Item 4)
      Title: Cheshire Cat
      Description: An imaginative jigsaw puzzle with big pieces for little fingers.
      Dimensions: 12"x8"
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 2/8, 1971 (Box 31, Item 5)
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 3/8, 1971 (Box 31, Item 6)
      Title: Tweedledee and Tweedledum
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 4/8, 1971 (Box 31, Item 7)
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 5/8, 1971 (Box 31, Item 8)
      Title: The Mad Hatter
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 6/8, 1971 (Box 31, Item 9)
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 7/8, 1971 (Box 31, Item 10)
      Title: Alice Holding a Pig
    - Colorforms Storybook Puzzle 8/8, 1971 (Box 31, Item 11)
    - Alice and the Mad Hatter Puzzle, [Undated] (Box 31, Item 12)
      Title: Alice and the Mad Hatter Puzzle
      Description: Two Puzzles, one side is Alice holding a pig, the other side is the Mad Hatter.
      Dimensions: 12"x18"
    - Alice and the Mad Hatter Puzzle, [Undated] (Box 31, Item 13)
      Description: Two Puzzles, one side is Alice holding a pig, the other side is the Mad Hatter. The Mad Hatter is missing six puzzle pieces.
    - Alice Wooden Croquet Set, 1987 (Box 34, Item 1)
      Title: Alice Wooden Croquet Set
      Description: Set consists of 2 mallets, 2 balls, and six figures painted after Tenniel.
    - Woodette Library - Edition Number 4, [1940's] (Box 35, Item 1)
      Title: Woodette Library - Edition No. 4
      Description: Set contains 6 story dolls, one of which is Alice. Designed by Mary Alice Stoddard.
- Oversize Series V: Printed Ephemera
  - Subseries B: Print Ephemera
    - Alice's Adventures Under Ground: Excerpts from the Original Lewis Carroll Manuscript in the British Museum, 1965 (Box 26, Item 1)
      Title: Alice's Adventures Under Ground: Excerpts from the Original Lewis Carroll Manuscript in the British Museum
      Description: Circular jigsaw-puzzle, publisher's circular (cylindrical) box 14¼ inches (diameter) printed in black and white-reserve on salmon-pink ground.
      Dimensions: 20.25" diameter
    - Advertisement from Dairy-Deli Wonderland of Values Sweepstakes, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Alice in Wonderland Magazine Advertisements, [1940's] (Box 47, Folder 7)
      Title: Alice in Wonderland Magazine Advertisements
      Description: Includes the Original Alice, 7 full-page individual advertisements printed in the Field Magazine over a period of several months in 1949. The artists are identified only as Hanna (5 ads) and Gilroy (2 ads) All of the ads, continue the clever Guinness Alice parodies. And "Oh Mother! Cried Alice. Here's the new Philco fridge" advertisement.
    - Alice in Wonderland Prints, [Undated] (Box 38, Folder 1)
      1. Cheshire Cat Print. 2. Alice in Wonderland House Print. 3. Wonderland Print by John Anthony Miller. 4. Lewis Carroll Print. 5. Lewis Carroll Print.
      Dimensions: 1. 10"x13". 2. 5"x6.5". 3. 6"x 6.5". 4. 9"x12". 5. 9"x12".
    - Alice in Wonderland Prints, [Undated] (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Title: Alice in Wonderland Prints
      Description: 1. Alice Pleasance Liddell. A calligraphic rendering of the Carroll poem the End Looking-Glass. 2. Lewis Carroll's Jabberwocky, a Zalben poster issued by Warne to publicize the book. 3. Scribner's American Painter's Series, No. 3, Down the Rabbit Hole by Saul Schary. 4. The Cheshire Cat.
      Dimensions: 1. 8"x17". 2. 12"x20". 4. 14"x16".
    - Alice in Wonderland Prints, [Undated] (Box 53, Folder 6)
      Description: 1. Sepia print of Charles Lewis Dodgson. 2. How Doth the Little Crocodile, by Sarah Chamberlain. Calligraphic reproduction with white ink on black background of Alice's recitation in the pool of tears. 3. Psychedelic Caterpillar smoking his hookah, by Jonathan. 4. Alice au Pays des Merveilles, Disney Studios, RKO Films. 4-color poster advertising the exhibition of the Disney film in France.
      Dimensions: 1. 11"x15". 2. 15"x16" 3. 18"x20" 4. 13"x17"
    - Alice in Wonderland Prints, [Undated] (Box 53, Folder 8)
      Description: 1. Alice. 2. Life Magazine Poster board Print of Humpty Dumpty. 3. Yellow Lewis Carroll Exhibition Poster. 4. Fantasy, an Alice in Wonderland Artist's Proof by John A. Miller.
      Dimensions: 1. 20"x15". 2. 19.5"x24.5". 3. 11.5"x10". 4. 18"x23".
    - Alice in Wonderland Prints, [Undated] (Folder 3)
      Description: 1. Beyond the Looking Glass of the Patty Hurst Trial by Ralph Steadman, 4 page proof for Rolling Stone Magazine. 2. Alice in Wonderland. 3. Pig n' Pepper by Juan Ripley. 4. Bill Osco's Alice in Wonderland, an X-Rated Musical Comedy. 5. Pool of Tears by Juan Ripley. 6. Croquet Ground by Juan Ripley. 7. Alice and the Caterpillar by Juan Ripley. 8. Pig n' Pepper by Juan Ripley. 9. Alice in Wonderland by Beck Gaurue.
      Dimensions: 1. 23.75"x18". 2. 36.25"x24.75". 3. 34.5"x22". 4. 31"x25". 5. 39"x15". 6. 39"x15". 7. 34.5"x22". 8. 34.5"x22". 9. 28.5"x22.
    - Alice in Wonderland Prints, [Undated] (Folder 4)
    - Alice in Wonderland Prints, [Undated] (Folder 2)
      Description: 1. Alice in Wonderland Poster. 2. Alice in Wonderland Poster. 3. Production of Alice in Wonderland at the "Teatr Rozmaitosci W.Warszawie". 4. Cheshire Cat Poster "We Are All Mad." 5. 3 Posters with sketches of Alice in Wonderland Characters. 6. Alice's Tea Party Poster. 7. 4 Posters with Alice in Wonderland Scenes. 8.Cheshire Cat Poster "We Are All Mad".
      Dimensions: 1. 36.25"x24.75". 2. 36.25"x24.75". 3. 37"x25" 4. 34.5"x23" 5. 23"x17.5" 6. 23.5"x17.5". 7. 35"x25.5". 8. 34.5"x23"
    - Alice in Wonderland Restaurant Menu and Place Mat, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Companion-Guide to the Exhibition Alice at Longleat, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Fashions of the Hour Magazine, 1938 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Lewis Carroll's Alice's Adventures in Wonderland; the Newberry Library Calendar for 1982 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Manitoba Theatre Centre Education Kit for Alice Through the Looking Glass, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Thirteen Prints Illustrated by John Tenniel from Alice in Wonderland and Alice Through the Looking Glass, [Undated] (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Subseries C: Posters
    - 9. Alice in the White Rabbit's Room and 10. Alice Plays at Croquet, Undated (Flat-file-folder [small folder])
      Dimensions: 32"x23"
      2 posters - one is damaged
      Artist: Gertrude Demain Hammond
    - Alice and the White Rabbit Psychedelic Poster by Steve Sachs, [1960's] (Flat-file-folder [small folder])
      Dimensions: 35"x23"
    - Alice in Wonderland page proof, [Undated] (Flat-file-folder 2)
      Dimensions: 38"x27"
    - Alice in Wonderland Posters, [Undated] (Box 38, Folder 3)
      1. Lewis Carroll Exhibit at Pratt Institute Library, celebrating the 100th anniversary of Alice in Wonderland, designed by Willa Percival. 2. Forest Theatre Production of Pygmalion and Galatea and Alice in Wonderland. 3. Alice in Wonderland Presented by the Young People's Theater.
      Dimensions: 1. 13"x 16.5". 2. 11"x 15.5". 3. 17"x 11".
    - Alice in Wonderland Posters, [Undated] (Box 53, Folder 3)
      1. Children's Play of the Season, Forest Theatre Presents Alice in Wonderland. 2. The Bay Theater Collective Presents Alice in Wonderland and Through the Looking Glass.
      Dimensions: 1. 12.5"x21". 2. 13"x18.5".
    - Alice in Wonderland Posters, [Undated] (Box 53, Folder 4)
      1. Children's Theater of Portland presenting "Alice in the Wonderland of Pooh". Pickard Theater on the Bowdoin College campus. 2. Hollywood Bowl, color poster for 60th anniversary season, 1981, depicting a bright White Rabbit against the background of Hollywood.
      Dimensions: 1. 22"x14" 2. 22"x14".
    - Deaf Alice Poster, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      Dimensions: 12"x17"
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland RKO Film Poster Depicting Enlarged Tea Party, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Dimensions: 14"x36"
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Technicolor Posters, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      1. Alice and the Tweedles. 2. The White Rabbit. 3. The Queen of Hearts and the Cheshire Cat. 4. The Mad Hatter and the Tea Cup.
      Dimensions: 1. 11"x13". 2. 11"x13". 3. 11"x13". 4. 11"x13".
    - Large Alice in Wonderland posters (Folder 1)
    - Japanese stage plays, 1998-2002 (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 19)
    - Jan Švankmajer's Něco z Alenky, 1987 (Box Shared Fales 003, Folder 13)
    - Ulysse, Alice, Oh! Hisse exhibit, 1978 (Flat-file-folder [large folder])
    - Walt Disney presents Alice nel Paese delle Meraviglie, 1951; cuid6203 (Item MSS.368.cuid6203)
    - Alice's Adventures in Wonderland in emoji, Undated (Flat-file-folder [large folder])
    - Down the Rabbit Hole, Dartmouth College's 2007 Winter Carnival (Box Shared Fales 001, Folder 10)
- Oversize Series VII: Books/Magazines/Clippings/Newspapers
  - Subseries E: Activity Books
    - Alice in Wonderland; a Giant Coloring Book, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Alice in Wonderland; a Giant Coloring Book, [Undated] (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book, [Undated] (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - The Colorful Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book, [Undated] (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Kim's Storybook Friends Coloring Book; Six Delightful Storybook Characters to Color, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Paper Doll Storybook Kiddles, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      6 dolls with stands and press out dresses and 6 storybook scenes to press out and set up. One of the dolls is Alice in WonderLiddle.
    - Stand-Ups; Adventures of Alice in Wonderland, [Undated] (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Sticker Fun; Stencil and Coloring Book, 1951 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Subseries F: Newspapers
    - The London Times, [1865-1972] (Box 25)
- Oversize Series VIII: Art
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 1/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 1)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 1/26
    Description: Cover, Frontspiece, Bibliography.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 2/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 2)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 2/26
    Description: Headpiece for Forward.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 3/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 3)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 3/26
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 4/36, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 4)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 4/26
    Description: Headpiece for Biography.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 5/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 5)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 5/26
    Description: Headpiece for "Little Known Facts--".
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 6/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 6)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 6/26
    Description: Headpiece for Introduction.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 7/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 7)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 7/26
    Description: Alice sat nodding sleepily on a mossy bank beside her big sister, who was reading.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 8/36, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 8)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 8/26
    Description: Crocodile: Danger from pirates, or robbers, or deceitful creditors.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 9/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 9)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 9/26
    Description: Looking-Glass: Mirror; for a girl - she is jilted at the church door.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 10/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 10)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 10/26
    Description: Wood: If you dream that you are walking along in an extensive wood, it denotes that you will quickly fall in love and also that you will be often married.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 11/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 11)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 11/26
    Description: Caterpillar: You will soon witness some marvelous spiritual phenomena.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 12/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 12)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 12/26
    Description: Nest: bird's nest; for a young woman, this dream foretells a change of abode.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 13/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 13)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 13/26
    Description: Frog: Neglect, lack of interest in your work, slovenliness in dress and in manner.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 14/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 14)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 14/26
    Description: Whistling: Gives prediction of a sensational fire, or storm within a week from now.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 15/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 15)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 15/26
    Description: Baby: To dream you had to take a baby, is a hint to fulfill the dream at your earliest possible convenience.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 16/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 16)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 16/26
    Description: Treacle: Beware of excessive heat.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 17/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 17)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 17/26
    Description: Tea: To sip or drink tea, gives promise that you will yet secure the secret of long life, that you may live one hundred years or more.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 18/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 18)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 18/26
    Description: Procession: You shall be the gainer or guardian of property; you shall be the parent of a son who will be an illustrious warrior. He will cause pain, but will be a mighty noble.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 19/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 19)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 19/26
    Description: Club: To dream of a club, denotes short imprisonment which will bring you no disgrace. You will only save money.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 20/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 20)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 20/26
    Description: Game: To dream of playing ball denotes you will be seized for gambling.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 21/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 21)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 21/26
    Description: Reading: To dream of reading, denotes a pleasure trip on which you will get secret information about a plan which will yield you prosperity.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 22/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 22)
    Description: Shoes: Practical jokes and unwise, harsh criticism alienate your dearest friends from you.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 23/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 23)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 22/26